They're developing quickly! They're absolutely superhuman!
إنهم يتطورون بسرعة هائلة أبناؤك جنود خارقون بحق
– Father! – Father dearest!
أبي - أبتي -
I'm so proud of all of you!
أنا فخورٌ بكم
My beloved children!
يا أبنائي الأعزاء
Where do they take the fancy food we've been making?
أين يذهبون بذلك الطعام الفاخر في موعد كل وجبة؟
I'm not sure. There aren't any guests in the castle.
لا أعلم، ليس لدينا أي ضيوف
Don't be nosy! His Majesty ordered us to cook, so we're going to cook.
لا تكونا فضوليتين، فهذه أوامر جلالة الملك نحن نطهو ما نؤمر به وحسب
Sanji!
سانجي
Royalty mustn't serve anyone! How many times do I have to tell you this?!
كم مرة عليّ إخبارك بأنّ الملوك لا يخدمون أحدًا؟
Your mother is dead!
والدتك ماتت بالفعل
Stop chasing her shadow!
كفّ عن تقليد أفعال الموتى
Ouch!
مؤلم
Oh, boy!
يا للهول
– Ow, ow, ow! – Are you all right, Your Highness?!
مؤلم، مؤلم - هل أنت بخير يا سانجي-ساما؟ -
His Majesty ordered us not to allow you into the kitchen.
أخبرنا جلالة الملك بعدم السماح لك بالتواجد في المطبخ
Please!
أرجوك
Let me... stay!
من فضلك، هلّا تركتني
It's done!
اكتمل
– Where are you going all on your own? – To see my mother.
أين ستذهب وحدك؟ - لزيارة أمي -
The medical ward is at the far end, and the weather is...
...العنبر الطبي في أقصى النهاية، والطقس الحالي
– I can do it. – But...
سأنجح - ولكن -
Don't follow me!
لا تتبعني
And don't tell my father.
ولا تخبر أبي
Get back inside!
عودوا إلى المنازل
What?! This isn't your food!
ماذا تريد؟ هذا ليس طعامك
S-Stop!
توقف
Y-Your Highness!
سـ-سانجي-ساما
Did you come here all on your own?!
أيعقل أنك وحدك؟
I appreciate the sentiment.
ما فعلته يسعدني
But we can't let Her Majesty's stomach hurt.
ولكن لا يمكننا التسبب بآلام المعدة لجلالة الملكة
Still, maybe it tastes better than it...
ولكن ربما مذاقه لذيذ
Sanji!
سانجي
Did you come to visit me in this storm?
هل جئت لزيارتي في هذا المطر؟
If your father finds out, he'll be furious.
سيغضب والدك إن علم بالأمر
This is from Prince Sanji.
هذه الوجبة من سانجي-ساما
Did you make this for me?
هل أعددتها لأجلي؟
Époni!
...إيبوني
Y-Yes, Your Majesty!
حاضرة يا جلالتك
Don't be presumptuous! Hand over what Sanji cooked for me!
لا تتصرفي كما يحلو لكِ، أحضري ما أعدّه سانجي لي حقًّا
Well, okay.
بشأن هذا... مفهوم
But it was damaged on his way here, so I threw it in the trash.
ولكنه تضرر في طريقه إلى هنا، لذا ألقيته في القمامة
– Bring it to me! – Yes, ma'am!
أحضريه - حاضر -
Wow, nice!
يبدو شهيًّا
Scrambled eggs, fish, and bananas?
بيض ملفوف وسمكة وموزة؟
I'm sorry, Mother!
عذرًا يا أمي
I messed it up!
فشلت
I tripped and dropped it on my way here.
تعثرتُ في طريقي إلى هنا وأسقطته
It's been crushed and got wet in the rain.
وتعرض للسحق، وتبلل بسبب المطر
Let's try it.
لنجرب
Yummy!
لذيذ
– Really?! – Yes!
حقًّا؟ - أجل -
Mother!
أمي
Sanji, will you cook for me again?
سانجي، هلّا طهوت لأجلي مجددًا
You want cookbooks and utensils?
تريد كُتبًا لتعليم الطهي وأدوات مطبخ؟
"All... Blue"?
أول بلو؟
"Where fish from all four seas live,"
«حيث تعيش أسماك البحار الأربعة»
"a legendary sea"!
«بحرٌ أسطوريّ»
See! I told you Sanji was down here.
انظروا، إنه سانجي كما توقعت
You're right! That's totally him!
أنت محق، إنه هو فعلًا
So he's still alive after all! Why did Father lie to us?
إذًا هو لا يزال حيًّا، ولكن لماذا كذب علينا والدنا؟
Probably because he wishes he were dead.
لأنه يتمنى موته
In that case, if he really dies, will Father be happy?
إذًا سيكون والدنا سعيدًا إن مات بالفعل، أليس كذلك؟
Stop it!
توقفوا
You're a failure who deserves to die, Sanji!
أنت فاشل يستحق الموت، أليس كذلك يا سانجي؟
Ow...
...مؤلم
Don't assume that I'm on your side. I don't want to get dragged into this!
لا تظن بأنني حليفتك، لا أريد التورط بالأمر
Those three are Father's ideal soldiers.
أولئك الثلاثة هم محاربي والدي المثاليين
They lack emotions like pity, sympathy, and even sadness.
لا يشعرون بالشفقة أو الحزن إنهم متجردون من المشاعر
My body was successfully augmented, but that's one area where I'm different from them.
تمّ تعديل جسدي بنجاح، ولكن ذلك هو الفارق بيني وبينهم
See you later.
إلى اللقاء
Th-Thank you, Reiju.
شكرًا يا ريجو
Oh, right. We climb the Red Line soon.
بالمناسبة، سنتسلق الريد لاين قريبًا
We're going to wage war in the East Blue.
يبدو أننا سنخوض حروبًا في الأزرق الشرقي
War?
حرب؟
Set course for the East Blue!
حددوا الوجهة نحو الأزرق الشرقي
The estimate arrival time is three weeks.
وقت السفر التقديري هو ثلاثة أسابيع
Reiju, I...
...ريجو، أنا
I...
...أنا
want to be a cook!
أريد أن أكون طاهيًا
Fire!
أطلقوا
– It's Germa 66. – What?! They're real?!
إنهم جيرما 66 - ماذا قلت؟ أهم حقيقيون؟ -
What's going on?!
ما الذي يجري؟
Generalissimo Judge, our targets in Cozia have noticed us!
جادج-ساما، تمّ رصد وجودنا من قبل هدفنا مملكة كوجيا
Crush them!
حطموهم
So, like I said, don't tell me something like that!
ألم آمرك بعدم إخباري بهذا؟
If I can... while in the East Blue...
...في هذا الأزرق الشرقي
If I can escape,
...إن أمكنني الهرب
I'll never have to see...
...فلن أضطر بعد الآن لأن أرى
Father's face...
...وجه أبي
ever again, right?
أليس كذلك؟
Step back!
تراجع
This is your only chance!
هذه فرصتك الوحيدة
Don't screw up!
لا تفشل بها
Go ashore!
انطلقوا إلى اليابسة
It's just begun!
بدأ الغزو
The key to your iron mask is in our father's room! Go get it!
مفتاح قناعك الحديدي في غرفة والدنا، اذهب لإحضاره
I'm gonna go see what's going on outside!
سأذهب لتفقد الوضع في الخارج
Okay?!
مفهوم؟
Y-Yeah!
أجل
When you get into his room, look for a skull symbol on the wall!
عندما تدخل غرفة والدنا، ابحث عن رمز جمجمة على الحائط
You'll find a safe there!
هناك ستجد بابًا سريًّا
I got it!
نجحت
What are you doing over there?
ماذا تفعل هناك؟
Sanji-kun, why are you here?!
لِمَ أنت هنا يا سانجي؟
Father...
أبتي
I'm leaving this country! Don't try to stop me!
سأغادر هذه المملكة، لا تعق طريقي
It seems your imprisonment has harshened your words.
أصبحت وقحًا خلال فترة حبسك
An ordinary boy such as yourself has no chance of surviving in this or any other sea.
ليس من السهل على طفل عادي مثلك النجاة وحده في بحر هائج كهذا
You will die!
ستموت
So what?! You can't stop me!
وماذا في ذلك؟ لا يمكنك منعي
That's a relief!
هذا مطمئن
I guess I'm human after all.
أنا إنسان في نهاية المطاف
Even though you're useless, I couldn't bring myself to kill my own son.
رغم كونك فاشلًا، إلّا أنني لا يمكنني قتلك لأنك ابني
But you want to leave on your own?
ولكن هل سترحل من تلقاء نفسك؟
I will not stop you. Take the key to that iron mask and leave.
لن أمنعك، وبوسعك أخذ مفتاح القناع الحديدي
But I have one more thing to ask as your father, Sanji.
ولكن هل يمكنني طلب معروف أخير منك بصفتي والدك يا سانجي؟
Don't ever admit that I'm your father...
...حقيقة أنني والدك
to even a single person!
إيّاك والإقرار بها أمام أحد
I do not want anyone to learn of my shame.
إنه عار لا أريد لأحد أن يعرف بشأنه
Do you understand?
أفهمت؟
What should we do about the cruise ship at the port?!
ماذا عن سفينة الرحلات الراسية عند الميناء؟
They aren't our target! There's just in the wrong place! Leave them alone!
لا علاقة لنا بها، فهي مجرد سفينة سيئة الحظ، دعوها وشأنها
Get on that ship!
اركب تلك السفينة
Sanji! You're a boy! Stop crying already!
سانجي، أنت رجل، كفّ عن البكاء
Listen! Don't ever come back here!
أنصت، إياك والعودة إلى هنا مجددًا
Uh-huh!
حسنًا
The sea's a huge place! You'll...
...البحر واسع، ويومًا ما
You'll definitely find people who will accept you!
يومًا ما، حتمًا ستقابل أشخاصًا يعاملونك بطيبة
Run!
اركض
Don't look back!
لا تنظر للخلف
Run! Sanji!
اركض يا سانجي
Yummy! It's nice and crunchy!
لذيذ، ويذوب بالفم
Yes!
عظيم
He ate Minister Cracker's biscuit soldiers!
التهم محاربي البسكويت التابعين لكراكر-ساما
What?!
ماذا؟
How dare you eat them!
كيف لك أن تتناولهم؟
Biscuits are food!
البسكويت طعام
That's right, Luffy! Once you eat them, they can't come back!
هذا صحيح يا لوفي، ولا يمكنهم العودة حالما تلتهمهم
Eat as many of them as you can!
تناول قدر رغبتك
What a crafty woman!
يا لها من امرأة ذكية-جو
Oh, no. Is he conscious?
مصيبة، ألا يزال واعيًا؟
Get out of my way.
ابتعدوا
Oh, Lady Reiju, we're about to treat his...
ريجو-ساما، سنعالجه فورًا
I said get out of my way!
ألم تسمعوني أقول ابتعدوا؟
I'm sorry!
المعذرة
Good grief.
،اتعبتني
Are you going to meet your fiancée with that face?
هل ستذهب لرؤية خطيبتك بهذا الوجه؟
This could've all been avoided if you had just forgotten about that restaurant owner.
كان بإمكانك تجنب هذا الموقف لو تخليت عن مالك المطعم الذي كنت تعمل لديه
Why did you come back?
لماذا عدت؟
I thought that you wanted to forget about this place?
...ظننتُ أنك لم ترغب بتذكر هذا المكان مجددًا
Sanji.
يا سانجي
I-I'm stuffed now.
امتلأتُ على آخري
Screw you!
كفاك عبثًا
I'm sick of fighting you already!
سئمت وتعبت من قتالك
You fight, run away, then come back and eat!
تقاتل وتهرب، ثم تعود وتأكل
Is he really human?!
أهو بشري حقًّا؟
Minister Cracker is amazing, but so is Straw Hat's appetite!
كراكر-ساما مدهش، ولكن شهية قبعة القش مدهشة كذلك
Minister Cracker...
كراكر-ساما
Hey, are his biscuits really infinite?
هل بسكويته لا نهائي حقًّا؟
Yes, that's right.
هذا صحيح-جو
But his stamina can't be!
ولكن طاقته ستصل إلى حدودها
I'll outlast you!
بل أنت من سيصل إلى حدوده
Eat until you burst! Then your comrades will give up!
تناول حتى تنفجر، وحينها ستتخلى عن صديقك أخيرًا
I'll eat every last one!
لن أتخلى عنه
I'll eat and eat and take Sanji back!
بل سأتناول وأتناول وسأذهب لرؤية سانجي
I'll bring out more biscuit soldiers for you, then.
إذًا سآتيك بالمزيد من محاربي البسكويت كما تشاء
Eat them and pop, Straw Hat!
تناولهم وانفجر يا قبعة القش
And...
...وكذلك
I'll tell Mama that you aided them, Kingbaum!
سأخبر ماما بأنكم ساعدتمهما يا كينغبوم
What?! But you already chopped off the top of my head!
ماذا؟ ولكنك قطعت فروة رأسي بالفعل
That's not fair, Minister Cracker!
هذا ليس عدلًا يا كراكر-ساما
She's using the power of Mama's vivre card against us!
نحن في رهبة من الفيفر الكارد الخاصة بماما والتي تمتلكه هذه الفتاة-جو
So, in a way, we are obeying Mama!
بعبارة أخرى، نحن نطيع ماما
Save your excuses for Mama! The fact is, you interfered with my mission!
،وفروا أعذاركم إلى أن تقابلوا ماما الحقيقة هي أنكم اعترضتم طريقي
If it weren't for her rain, my hard biscuit soldiers
...لولا أمطار تلك المرأة وخطتها، لما تحول محاربو البسكويت الأصلاب
wouldn't have softened up into tasty, chewable snacks!
إلى وجبات خفيفة شهية وسهلة التفتت
Shut up! This is a fight between pirates!
اخرس، فهذه معركة بين قراصنة
We figured out your weakness, but that doesn't mean you should take it out on my soldiers!
لا يعني اكتشافنا لنقطة ضعفك أن تلقي باللوم على جنودنا
Your?!
ماذا؟
Are we...
جنودنا؟
...her soldiers now?!
هل أصبحنا جنود تلك المرأة الآن؟
What was that?
ما الأمر؟
We're sorry!
نعتذر
Let's put an end to this, biscuit soldiers!
فلنضع حدًّا لهذه المعركة يا محاربي البسكويت
This should end it!
حانت النهاية
I guess I gotta eat them. They'll keep coming if I break them.
ما بيدي خيار سوى تناولهم، لأنهم سيعودون حتى إن حطمتهم
But...
...ولكن
I'm getting pretty full now.
لأكون صادقًا فقد وصلت لأقصى حدودي
Make sure to protect me, homies!
احرصوا على حمايتي جيدًا يا هوميز
G-Got it!
حـ-حاضر
Hey, Nami, can I try something other than eating them?
...نامي، هل يمكننا تجربة شيء آخر غير تناولهم
I'll fight them for a while, and then continue.
بينما أذهب لتحطيمهم ثم أعود؟
Weather Egg!
بيضة الطقس
I don't care if you're related to an emperor...
لا أعلم ما تكون صلتك بالإمبراطورة
Luffy's going to be the pirate king!
ولكن لوفي هو من سيصير ملك القراصنة
So there's no limit to his appetite!
بعبارة أخرى، لا حدود لشهيته
What?! Nami, I've been eating all night!
...ماذا؟ نامي، لقد كنتُ آكل طوال هذا الوقت
Is his stomach bottomless?
كيف يعقل ذلك؟ هل معدته بلا حدود؟
No...
...لا
Rain Spark!
شرارة المطر
The soldiers are going to soften up again! Stop!
سيتحول المحاربون إلى بسكويت طري مرة أخرى
No... I can't...
...لا، لم أعد
Wait for me, Sanji!
انتظرني يا سانجي
Dammit!
أيها الأوغاد
Look at that gluttony!
يا لها من طريقة في الأكل
Generalissimo Judge, it is time.
جادج-ساما، حان الوقت
The preparations are complete.
اكتملت الاستعدادات
Good, inform my children.
حسنًا، أخبروا أبنائي
We're leaving for Whole Cake Chateau!
سنرحل إلى قصر الكعكة الكاملة
Ready? This might sting a little.
هل أنت جاهز؟ سيؤلمك
Just hurry up and do it.
أسرعي بوضعه
It feels a little weird...
يوخز قليلًا
Don't touch it.
لا تلمسه
How does it feel?
كيف تشعر؟
The swelling has gone down.
اختفى التورم
Ouch!
مؤلم
That pack only works for swelling.
إنه قناع للوجه مخصص للتورم
It's suppressing the body's normal response, so it's actually preventing it from healing.
يقمع استجابة الجسد الطبيعية لكنه لا يعالجها
But it's better than your fiancée seeing your swollen face.
ولكنه أفضل من رؤية خطيبتك لوجهك المتورم
The members of the Charlotte family don't take their spouses' family name.
أعضاء عائلة شارلوت لا يغيرون أسماءهم بعد الزواج
So if they accept you as a part of their family, you can live a happy life.
لذا ستكون حياتك سعيدة إن قبلوك بينهم
Damn you...
...أيتها اللعينة
You came back on your own. I don't owe you anything.
لقد عدت بإرادتك، لا تنتظر مني فعل شيء
You won't get another chance.
ما من فرصة ثانية
By the way, where did you pick up that sense of chivalry?
على أي حال، من أين أتيت بتلك الشهامة؟
Women! Women! Women! Women!
امرأة، امرأة، امرأة، امرأة
Women!
امرأة
Shut up! We don't need a female chef!
صمتًا، لسنا بحاجة لطاهية امرأة
Cut it out!
اخرسوا
I'm the type of man that reinforces my lessons through kicks.
أنا أُعلّم الطهاة عبر الركل
I can't do that to a woman!
ولا يمكنني فعل ذلك لامرأة
Why not?! If she doesn't listen, then just kick her, too!
لماذا؟ إن لم تتعلم فلا بأس بركلها
You idiot!
أيها الأحمق
Ouch!
مؤلم
A man can't kick a woman!
على الرجل ألّا يركل امرأة
That's been the rule since the age of the dinosaurs!
هذا هو المنطق السائد منذ عصر الديناصورات
Listen, little eggplant!
أنصت أيها القزم
You can make all kinds of mistakes as a human being!
يمكنك ارتكاب أي عدد من الأخطاء لأنك بشري
But if you ever fail at being a proper man,
ولكن إن تجرأت على خيانة شرف الرجولة
I'll cut off your balls, and slit my own throat!
فسأقطع خصيتيك من جذريهما وسأقطع رأسي كذلك
What?! Why would you do that to yourself?!
ماذا؟ لماذا ستقطع رأسك أيها العجوز؟
That's how a parent owns up to their mistake!
تلك هي الطريقة التي يدفع بها الوالد الثمن
You fool... Don't become the type of person I despise.
لا تتحول إلى شخص أكرهه أيها الأحمق
Now, get back to work.
والآن عُد إلى العمل
That's been the rule since the age of the dinosaurs.
إنها أحد التقاليد من عصر الديناصورات
Sanji, Your Highness, it's time to leave.
سانجي-ساما، حان وقت الرحيل
You all are going to the engagement ceremony at Whole Cake Chateau.
سيُعقد حفل الخطوبة في قصر الكعكة الكاملة
Put this shirt on.
ارتدِ هذا القميص
You're a member of the Vinsmoke royal family.
أنت أحد أفراد عائلة فينسموك
You need to look the part.
ولا بدّ لمظهرك أن يعبّر عن ذلك
What a joke...
يا للسخافة
Meanwhile, in Brûlée's Mirro-world...
في الوقت ذاته داخل عالم مرايا بروليه
I found you!
عثرت عليكما
She's back!
لقد عادت
You can't escape!
لا مهرب لكما
I can't run anymore, Chobro!
لم يعد بإمكاني الركض يا تشونيكي
Stop running around all of my mirrors!
كفّا عن الركض بداخل المرايا
Have a great wedding ceremony!
استمتعوا بيوم الزفاف
Congratulations!
خالص تهانينا
Prince Sanji!
سانجي-ساما
Today is a new beginning for the Vinsmoke family.
هذا اليوم يعتبر بداية جديدة لنا نحن عائلة فينمسوك
Wave to the citizens, Sanji.
بادل المواطنين التحية يا سانجي
Let's go, guys!
فلنذهب يا رفاق
I've had enough, you guys!
هذا يكفي يا هؤلاء
I seriously can't eat anymore!
قلتُ أنني لم أعد قادرًا على الأكل
At your limit, huh?
هل وصلت لحدودك؟
I'll never throw up something that I've eaten!
لا أريد تقيؤ ما تناولته مهما كان الثمن
Then, I'll make it easy for you by stabbing your belly!
سأشق بطنك إذًا لأسهّل عليك المهمة
Look out, Luffy!
احذر يا لوفي
That's it! I'm ending this now!
لهذا سأضع حدًّا لهذا النزال
Muscle Balloon!
بالون العضلات
What the...?!
ما هذا؟
Gear Fourth!
المحرك الرابع
Tankman: Stuffed Version!
الرجل الدبابة: الإصدار المُتخم
What?! He's huge!
ما هذا؟ إنه ضخم
You look quite different from your first transformation.
تبدو مختلفًا عن تحولك الأول
Can you fight with that big fat body?!
أيمكنك القتال بمثل هذا الجسد المترهل؟
How hard is he?!
ما مدى صلابته؟
You snot-nosed brat!
أيها الطفل المتعالي
Don't push your luck!
...لا تغتر بنفسك
Straw Hat!
يا قبعة القش
Honey...
عسل
Pretzel!
بريتزل
Not yet!
ليس بعد
With this thrust, you'll burst!
ستنفجر بفضل هذه الطعنة
Crush Pretzel!
سحق
Luffy!
لوفي
What is this? Is it hard or soft?
ما هذا؟ أهو صلب أم طري؟
Wha...? What the hell is this?!
مـ-ماذا هذا؟
Biscuit soldiers!
محاربي البسكويت
Rain!
المطر
Nami!
نامي
Don't make it rain on the biscuits anymore! They can stay hard!
لا تلقي بالماء على ما تبقى من البسكويت دعيهم يحافظون على صلابتهم
Okay!
حسنًا
I can't get out! What's he gonna do?!
لا يمكنني الخروج، ماذا سيفعل؟
I'll show you the power of a full stomach!
سأريك قوة الشبع
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Cannonball!
كرة المدفع